peace what's good family today i'll be
doing a product review on dr sabi sell
food specifically on the bonjou cbd
capsules and hair food oil for me it's
been a while since i've last purchased
from dr sabi sell food i would say since
2016 the products i used to get was the
tooth powder hair food oil the bonjou
and the green food capsules so i wanted
to stick with a few familiar products
that i used to get such as the bonjou
and hair food oil just to see if i
noticed there's any difference in
consistency or change in the quality and
i also wanted to try something new that
was never around when dr sabi was here
with us the cbd capsules after dr sebi
passed away there was a lot of question
or uncertainty about the products
whether they would remain the same
quality and even talks of the company
being compromised they even had to list
it on their faq which according to them
they're stating that the company is not
compromised it is still the same staff
selected and trained by dr sabi and the
staff is still managed by pablo medina
who was a partner along with dr sabi dr
sabi's passing had nothing to do with
why i stopped purchasing from them it
was more that i was stepping into a
field of learning more about herbs and
how i can create some of the compounds
myself i found it to be far more cost
efficient to purchase bulk herbs and you
know make your own tonics and compounds
anytime i do a product review i like to
speak on the company as a whole let's
talk about their website it's clean
straight to the point easy to find what
you're looking for from the jump the
products are there and the description
is listed underneath as well as the
price so you know what you're getting
into there's nothing hidden you don't
have to click into anything you could
just continue to scroll and i like that
nothing to do with the product but i
also like the fact that they have
informative blogs on there that you can
get an idea on how to better your health
it gives you the feeling that it's not
just about the herbs that you take but
your everyday habits that you create for
yourself
so as i'm scrolling on a website i'm
noticing that all of their products have
five star reviews all of your products
have five star reviews and i'm not even
looking for one star reviews i'm talking
the three or four star reviews there's
none it makes me wonder are they
filtering out some of the reviews and
just leaving all good reviews i placed
my order on wednesday night got a
notification that very same day that the
order has shipped and i got my product
the following week on a monday three
business days that's not bad at all so
we're good on shipping a lot of paper
placed inside the box so you can shake
it around and you're not going to hear
any rattling so it was packaged very
well the banjo and hair food oil was in
bubble wrap while the cbd capsules were
just in there the security ceilings were
on our products you know to maintain uh
freshness so that's great no issues
there let's talk about the products
starting with the hair food oil what it
does is it nourishes the scalp and hair
and they say it fights dandruff and
breakage and also supports natural hair
growth i love the fact that they use
simple ingredients
olive oil batana coconut oil and french
vanilla the smell and the consistency is
the same from what i can remember which
to me isn't a good thing i always
thought the hair food oil was a bit too
oily for me and ever since i got batana
oil myself and it's raw form i'm
wondering how much batana oil are they
actually using i feel like they used a
greater ratio of olive oil and coconut
oil nonetheless i found it to be a great
product because it is so oily a little
bit does go a long way i massage it into
my beard and scalp and smooth it along
my locks as well not a big fan of the
hair food oil as i used to be i just
wish i could get a better ratio of the
batana oil i wanted to really get a feel
of the products such as banju and the
cbd capsules to do so i wanted to
cleanse as much as possible before
actually trying the products just to get
a sense of how they are affecting me
what i did before trying dr sabe's
products was i
fasted mostly on liquids and if i did
eat it was mostly raw foods i ate a lot
of pears and then i drank a lot of
smoothies that just helped me cleanse
out any foods and make sure that none of
the products were counteracting with any
of the other things i still had within
my system so the banjo the banjo was
always one of my favorite products that
i purchased and it tastes horrendous
it's not as bad as some of the other
bitters out there you know the
combination of herbs you can kind of
taste everything in there in 2022 their
banjo still tastes the exact same from
what i can remember in this situation if
it's not broke don't fix it i'm glad
they didn't they say it's good for brain
health by helping improve focus and
concentration
reduce anxiety and stress which a lot of
us need today it also helps to relieve
pain and inflammation the ingredients
they use elderberry blue vervain burdock
root valerian root bubble wheat white
willow yellow duck their directions are
to shake well before using
you want to take two tablespoons of
banju in the morning and two tablespoons
in the evening it could be taken on an
empty stomach or after a meal for
children under one year of age you want
to take half of the recommended dosage
for children one year and over take full
dosage so i start work at six a.m and
sometimes i work overtime so i might get
off at 5 p.m or around 6 p.m each day
before work i would take a shot of banjo
and then around 2 30 3 30 p.m i would
take another shot and i do get a feel
that it did improve my focus it takes
the exact same from what i can't
remember before it has that bitterness
but yet a hint of sweetness to it i
believe that sweetness could be coming
from the elderberry it's not a thin
consistency it's a little thick the
first sip it could get dark for you me
personally i don't feel as gag worthy
but you know that bitterness can get you
you might have to chase it down with
some spring water another thing i feel
banjo is great for is if you're on a
fast journey it helps redirect your mind
if you ever experience
my light went out sorry another thing i
feel bondrew is great for is if you're
on a fast journey or just trying to make
better health decisions uh maybe
redirect some of your cravings anytime i
had a craving for something uh like a
sweet type of food or or a savory salty
food you take a shot of this and you
don't want nothing else after except
water it's a 8 fluid ounce bottle i've
been taking it for about a week now i
have about half a bottle left and i feel
good about it now the cbd capsules i
wanted to try the cbd capsules because
this is something new that they decided
to make you know some people feel that
cbd isn't really in alignment of what dr
sabi would have done or would have
agreed to had he still been here with us
and that i'm not certain because he did
smoke marijuana consuming marijuana like
whether it's via oil or crushing down
the herb and actually eating it is far a
better option than smoking it uh it gets
a little tricky and i'll be honest i'm
still informing myself about cbd and
hemp the only hemp anything i know of
really is hemp seeds and i love those
but nonetheless i wanted to try cbd and
get a feel of it i decided why not with
save sell food products they're saying
it's full spectrum cbd capsules it helps
reduce anxiety and stress which you know
i would assume that relieve pain and
inflammation and support a healthy
cardiovascular system the ingredients
used is raw hemp full aerial parts and
phytocannabinoid rich they say as a
supplement you want to take two capsules
twice a day sometimes i would take two
capsules all in the morning or i would
split it maybe take one in the morning
one in the evening there was a time
where i even took four by accident you
know i didn't feel no different i didn't
feel high and i'm pretty sure that's not
how cbd full spectrum works or or how
you're supposed to feel and i believe it
did help me relax a bit during my work
shift sometimes when i'm processing
claims i shake my leg after you've been
sitting there for hours you know i do
get a little antsy to where i have to do
some type of movement i noticed i wasn't
doing that as much while
using the cbd capsules i believe they
had a few other cbd products on their
website which
you know i'm curious uh you know this
definitely got me interested in cbd
hemp in general watch i'm going to do
more research on and yeah those are my
three product reviews so is it worth
purchasing dr sabi sell food products
today in the year 2022 yes the products
haven't changed therefore to this day is
still high quality you are getting gotta
love their accessibility easy to find
the products easy to contact them if
necessary i love their innovation with a
few new herbal mixes and hemp added to
the lineup as of today competition is
high so the price may seem steep to some
but that's my full review on the three
products purchased that day let me know
in the comments have you purchased from
dr sabi sell food what are your thoughts
on the products and if you have tried
them which ones have you purchased i
hope you found value in today's video
don't forget to check out the other
content here on youtube until next time
hey every time i look out i'm on my
lookout cause tripping no i ain't hoping
no sense in voting politicians all of
that hating don't be creating food in my
kitchen all of that talking without no
walking can't help my vision when i step